{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953418170","data":{"timestamp":" 946953418170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" 6d3d5304-48b9-4526-949d-7cb7e278872b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953423843","data":{"timestamp":" 946953423843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" 6d3d5304-48b9-4526-949d-7cb7e278872b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953446259","data":{"timestamp":" 946953446259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mishale_vile_mishale_tele"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953452967","data":{"timestamp":" 946953452966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" gingile_yale_makelele_gingile"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953459652","data":{"timestamp":" 946953459652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" gingile_tungule_gingile_miale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953466396","data":{"timestamp":" 946953466396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vidole_nozibele_pale"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953473092","data":{"timestamp":" 946953473092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" unywele_unywele_polepole_vidole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953480645","data":{"timestamp":" 946953480644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" unywele_unywele_polepole_vidole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953487304","data":{"timestamp":" 946953487304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tule_tule_kobole_vile"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953494007","data":{"timestamp":" 946953494006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_shule_vidole_alale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953500726","data":{"timestamp":" 946953500726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" zile_zile_alale_vile"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953507482","data":{"timestamp":" 946953507481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" alale_alale_netasile_polepole"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953514174","data":{"timestamp":" 946953514173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" unywele_makelele_zile_unywele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953527425","data":{"timestamp":" 946953527423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" unywele_makelele_zile_unywele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953537294","data":{"timestamp":" 946953537293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" unywele_makelele_zile_unywele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.le.show.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953553262","data":{"timestamp":" 946953553262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053136"," gameId":" a8b0939b-838e-4d80-9e56-71d9ab0c34f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.le.show.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" unywele_makelele_zile_unywele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}